- Where's Mon?
- She's at home..
putting up decorations
for Rachel's birthday party tonight.
- You're not helping?
- I tried..
but apparently singing "I Will Survive"
in a helium voice, not helping.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
Don't say that loud.
Gunther's gonna want to hug me.
Good news, everyone.
We finally found a nanny.
- This is Molly. Molly, Chandler, Joey.
- Hi.
Somebody's getting a little fussy.
You're damn right I am. I've been
waiting for a cookie for seven minutes.
Okay. You know what,
I'm just gonna take her outside.
- No, you stay. I'll do it.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Nice to meet you guys.
- Yeah, you too.
- Wow, Molly's just great.
- Yeah.
Yes, bravo on the hot nanny.
- What? You really think she's hot?
- Are you kidding?
If I wasn't married,
she'd be rejecting me right now.
Joey?
How do you think she's doing?
Am I the only one that doesn't think
she's hot? Ross?
- I mean, she's not unattractive, but..
- Right.
but hot?
Thank you.
Now that Rachel's gone?
So hot, I cried myself to sleep
last night.
Hey, Mike,
what's the capital of Peru?
- Lima.
- No.
It starts with a V
and ends with an X.
And hopefully with a T-O
in the middle.
You know, come to think of it,
the capital of Peru is "Vtox."
- Oh, God!
- What?
Okay. I don't want to freak you out
or anything..
but I just saw a rat
in your cupboard.
Oh, yeah. No, that's Bob.
Well, he's your pet rat?
Well, not so much a pet as, you know,
an occasional visitor..
who I put food out for.
Kind of like Santa.
Except Santa doesn't poop
on the plate of cookies.
You can't keep a rat in your apartment.
They're unsanitary.
I mean, they transmit leptospirosis
and hantavirus.
- What are those?
- I don't know..
but they don't sound
like spa treatments.
- You have to get rid of it.
- Okay, fine.
If it means that much to you,
I'll get rid of Bob.
Thank you.
It's so weird you think he's so gross,
yet you're willing to eat his crackers.
- Hello.
Gavin, I just want to say
thank you again..
for watching Emma yesterday
during the presentation.
I really owe you an apology.
- For what?
- When we first met, you know..
I thought you were pompous
and arrogant and obnoxious.
Is this your first apology?
No, I just mean, you know,
first impressions don't mean anything.
And I think you're a really good guy.
And I'm sorry that I misjudged you.
- Morning.
- Hello.
But you know what?
Hey, new day, new leaf.
I am just really, really happy..
I'm sorry. Obviously, Heather's ass
has something more important to say..
so I'll just wait till it's finished.
- What?
- I was giving you an apology..
and you were totally
checking her out.
I wasn't. I'm in fashion.
I was looking at her skirt.
Or was it pants? I didn't really see
what happened below the ass area.
Wow, you are really..
You're really a creep.
What do you care
if I was looking at her?
Are you jealous?
Oh, yeah. I'm jealous.
"Oh, Gavin. Please,
please look at my ass."
Stop looking at my ass!
I mean, I just think
you are totally inappropriate. Okay?
This is a work environment.
She's your subordinate.
But it was okay when you
slept with your old assistant, Tag?
That is totally different
for two reasons.
One: I didn't know
that you knew that.
And two: I wasn't some creep
staring at his ass.
We had a.. We had a deep,
meaningful relationship.
What was Tag's last name?
It was..
Oh, my God.
He didn't.. He didn't..
He didn't have a last name.
It was just Tag, you know,
like Cher or..
you know, Moses.
But it was a deep,
meaningful relationship.
You know what? My first impression
of you was absolutely right.
You are arrogant. You are pompous.
Morgan! Morgan!
- Tag's last name was Morgan!
- It was Jones.
What are you, his boyfriend?
- Man, I wish I had a nanny like you.
- You mean when you were a baby?
Sure.
Would you stop staring at her?
I wasn't staring.
I was leering.
What's the big deal with her?
Maybe she's attractive
in an obvious kind of way.
Yeah, obvious beauty's the worst.
You know, when it's right there
in your face.
Me, I like to have to work
to find someone attractive.
Makes me feel like I earned it.
Looks like Joey's doing all right
with her.
Yeah. Hey, that was nice of you guys
to back off..
and let Joey get the girl for once.
- I'm gonna take her to the apartment.
- Okay. I'll be home right after work.
- Okay.
- Okay, bye, Emma.
I love you.
- Bye.
They've elected me to talk to you
about the baby talk.
It's not so good.
I think it's sweet.
Bye, Emma!
Hey, listen, Joey. About Molly, I would
really prefer if you didn't go after her.
- Why not?
- It took months to find a good nanny.
And I wouldn't want anything to,
you know, drive her away.
So you think I'm just
gonna sleep with her..
and never call her again, and
things are gonna get uncomfortable?
Yeah, that sounds about right.
Come on, there are plenty
of other women out there.
Just forget about her, okay?
She's off-limits.
Oh, man! What'd you have to go
and say that for?
Now that you told me I can't have her,
makes me want her even more!
- What are you, a child?
- Yes!
It's true.
He's like a little boy, like Ben.
Just think of him
as a really, really, really horny Ben.
No!
Look, Joey, come on now.
For me, please.
Just try to focus your sexual energy
on someone else.
Fine.
Take me home.
Do you want a piece of this?
- Hey, Mikey.
- Hey, Phoebe.
- What are you doing?
- Setting rattraps.
- To kill Bob?
- No. No, to test his neck strength.
No, I don't want to kill him.
I thought we were gonna capture him..
and, you know, set him free
in the countryside..
where he could meet
a friendly possum..
and a wisecracking owl.
- Okay, okay. I'll throw away the traps.
- All right, I'll find Bob. I'll get him.
Bob? Bob?
Robert?
Wait, I think I hear him.
Oh, my God! Bob had babies!
Bob's a mom!
We'll have to think of a new name.
I don't know,
I kind of like "Bob" for a girl.
No, no. I mean, I'm not sure that we..
Oh, my God. We killed Bob?
Well, maybe it wasn't Bob.
Maybe it was a mouse.
Susie?
That's it?
It's over?
Who shot J.R.?
I have got to get a job.
What's up?
Seriously, dude. Three years ago.
Listen, can you do me a favor?
I'm gonna be out today.
Can you keep an eye on Joey..
make sure nothing happens
between him and Molly?
- You don't trust him?
- Well, no.
Some woman who sounded
a lot like Joey called earlier..
and asked for her daughter,
the "hot nanny."
Is this your long-term plan,
for me to run interference?
Because I could get a job any day now.
You do appear right on the cusp
of something.
Look, come on, man. I'm sure
he'll lose interest in a week or two..
but for now, could you please
just do this for me?
Fine, but don't blame me
if it doesn't work.
Because you know once Joey
sets his mind on something..
more often than not,
he's going to have sex with it.
Well, I mean,
we've gotta do something. Okay?
Nannies like her don't grow on trees.
- Picturing that tree?
- I am, yes.
Where you going, Joe?
For a walk.
You mind if I join you?
Actually, I'd rather be alone. You know,
I really need to organize my thoughts.
Your thoughts?
Plural?
All right, fine.
I only have one thought.
It's about the hot nanny!
I gotta see her!
- I'm afraid I can't let you do that, Joe.
- Now you're saying I can't see her?
You're killing me! She's forbidden fruit!
It's like, like..
like she's the princess
and I'm the stable boy.
Look, I know. She's the most
beautiful woman in the world.
I can hear you.
Could you set my pillow and blanket
on the couch for me, please?
Why are you doing this, huh?
Did Ross tell you not to let me
go over there?
Yes, as a matter of fact, he did.
So I can't let you go.
Interesting. Now there are obstacles.
Hot nanny and me against the world!
This is the stuff great novels
are made of.
- Great novels?
- Fine. Mediocre porn.
- Gavin Mitchell's office.
- Rachel Greene's office.
Give me that phone.
Hello, this is Rachel Greene.
How can I help you?
Okay then.
I'll pass you back to your son.
Hey, Mom.
No, that's just my secretary.
Excuse me, Gavin.
I have a question I need to ask you.
Mom, I'll call you later. Yeah.
- Yes?
- If you like looking at butts so much..
why don't you just go
look in a mirror?
Thank God you finally said that.
I saw you make a note on your pad
three hours ago.
- Man, I really bug you. Don't I?
- Oh, no. Please..
I don't care about you
enough to bug me.
In fact, from now on,
I'm going to take the high road..
and I'm going to be very, very nice
to you, you mama's boy..
starting right now.
- Hey, Rach.
- Hi.
- Ready for your birthday lunch?
- I am.
But first, Monica,
I would like to introduce you..
to my very talented colleague
and more importantly..
my wonderful friend, Gavin Mitchell.
- Pleased to meet you.
Are you coming to Rachel's party?
Oh, no, no, no, no. Gavin can't.
He already has plans..
most likely with his mother.
I don't mind. I'll cancel them. I would
never miss my secretary's birthday.
Why did you invite him?
I can't stand that guy!
- You were being so nice to him.
- I was faking it.
Can't you tell when I'm being fake?
Hey, Mr. Phillips. Nice suit.
Right there.
That was so fake!
Hey, Chandler, which do you like better..
the tuna tartare
or the mushroom empanadas?
- The pile of raw fish, or the tacos?
- Oh, the tacos. Definitely, the tacos.
I still can't believe you invited Gavin.
He is just the last person
I want to see.
You're welcome for the party.
I'm glad you're having a good time.
I hope he doesn't show up.
Of course he won't, the guy hates me.
- Does he?
- What?
Maybe he keeps bothering you
so much because he likes you.
It's like in first grade
when Skippy Lange would push me..
because he secretly
had a crush on me.
Monica, you think Skippy liked you?
Honey, all those boys had a bet
to see if he could knock you over.
- She's out. I'm gonna take her home.
- Okay. Thank you.
Bye, sweetheart.
Do you see what all the guys
see in her?
Wouldn't kick her out of bed.
No more vodka for me.
Hey, Rach. So can I sing
"Happy Birthday" to you now?
- Yeah, sure.
- All right.
See you later.
Hey, Rach. Somebody got you shoes.
Give me!
- Wow. Wow. Oh, my God!
- Careful! Careful!
These are my rat babies!
Yeah. We have rat babies now.
You brought rats
to my birthday party?
So this is what a stroke feels like.
Well, I had to bring them.
We killed their mother.
They're our responsibility now.
You know, they require constant care.
You should know that, you're a mother.
Are you comparing my daughter
to a rat?
No. Seven rats.
We should take them home.
We need to feed them.
You're gonna leave my party
to take care of a box of rats?
Well, I'm sorry, Rachel,
but I'm not like you. Okay?
Not everyone can afford help.
Hey, where the hell
are Joey and Molly?
I asked you to watch them.
I'm sorry. I got a little preoccupied.
Look, we have to stop them
before something happens.
Right behind you, big guy.
So you see, Molly,
what people don't understand..
is that acting is a discipline.
It takes a lot of hard work.
- So where'd you study?
- I didn't go to college.
- No, where'd you study acting?
- Molly, people don't study acting.
Molly, do you mind giving us
just a minute?
- Sure. I'll go check on Emma.
- Thanks.
Will the stable boy
never get the princess?
What do you think you were gonna do,
have sex with her here on my couch?
No. The leather sticks to my ass.
This isn't fair. What makes you think
I'm gonna sleep with her..
and then blow her off, huh?
Can't you guys open your minds to
the possibility that I actually like her..
and might want something real?
Look, the truth is, I haven't felt
this way about anyone since Rachel.
Okay?
I didn't think I could ever love again.
- Come on!
- Joe!
Hi. Is Molly here?
Yeah, yeah. Come on in. Molly?
- Hey. Guys, this is Tabitha.
- Hey.
- I'll see you tomorrow.
- Okay.
Well, Joey, I guess
we have no problem.
It's like my favorite fairy tale
come true.
The princess, the stable boy
and the lesbian.
Okay. Okay,
you start preparing the formula..
and I'll start changing the box.
And then we gotta put them
straight to bed.
When did we become
one of those couples..
whose lives revolve around
their rats?
Well, you know what?
They're our responsibility now.
Okay, fine.
These rats are our responsibility.
What happens when they mate
and there are hundreds?
Mate? They're all brothers and sisters.
Yeah, not such a problem with rats.
No, they're more of a "love the one
you're with" kind of animal.
No. Really?
Oh, my.. Get off your sister!
Oh, my God. What are we gonna do?
The.. We have seven rats.
So, what if each of them
has seven rats..
and then each of those
has seven rats? That's like..
That's math I can't even do!
What are we gonna do?
Well, I know this is gonna
sound crazy..
but we could
not let the box of rats ruin our lives.
Yeah, okay. I guess you're right.
All right, so we should just
give them away.
But to nice families with children
and reduced-fat Wheat Thins.
Those were Bob's favorites.
It's gonna be okay.
- You must think I'm crazy.
- No, I think you're sweet.
Good. This is just so hard.
It's hard for me to let them go.
I guess it just brings back memories,
you know..
from when I gave birth to my brother's
triplets and I had to give them up.
I haven't told you about that yet,
have I?
Thanks for the party, honey.
Should I help you clean up?
No way. You had your party.
Now I have mine.
- Is everything all right?
- I just get bummed..
when my birthday's over.
Well, at least you have one thing
to be happy about.
That jerk, Gavin, from your office
didn't show up.
Yeah, I hate him.
We weren't talking about you.
We were..
No. No way to recover. No. Okay.
- Fun party.
- Well, it was.
And you would have seen it
if you didn't show up at..
9:30?! God! This party was lame.
Again, you're welcome!
- Look, I'll just give you this and go.
- You bought me a present. Why?
Let me explain how birthday parties
usually work. There are presents..
and a cake,
perhaps a fourth or fifth person.
Okay, I..
I got you the present to make up
for being such a jerk to you.
Well, okay. Well, that's very nice.
And you wrote a card.
- "From Gavin."
- I really mean it.
It's beautiful.
If you don't mind..?
Let me.
Well, what do you know, it fits.
See, Gavin. You're capable of being
a nice guy.
Why do you give me such a hard time?
I'm not sure.
Well, Monica seems to think
it's because you have feelings for me.
I do have feelings for you.
- You do?
- Yes. I feel that you're a little annoying.
See, why? Gavin, why?
Right when I'm about to change
my opinion of you, you go and you..
And you do that.
Hey. Listen,
I think I left something here.
Well, somebody left this.
Is this yours?
No, but I like it.
No, I think I left one of my rat babies.
Well, no. I haven't seen it,
but if I do, I'll let you know.
Rat baby! Rat baby! Rat baby!
Rat baby!
Maybe that's him.